Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature were hurt during the
production of this show.
2 Days Later
Togay is Noyan's son, my Bey.
Noyan ha?
So, I was destined to hear that infidel's
name one more time before I die.
Our enemies are left for us by
our ancestors.
This is true, Osman Bey. We couldn't deal
with that devil with Ertugrul Bey, but...
You are going to kill him now,
in sha Allah ( If Allah permits).
His enemies raided his tent and
killed his family.
They captured his two brothers.
He escaped.
He grew up in the forest. People say
he drank pig milk.
Then an ominous shaman found him and
raise him.
-Is this why they call Togay black shaman?
-Yes my Bey.
- What about his brothers?
- Togay saved them.
Now they are working together.
I heard people were talking about
this when I was in Aleppo, my Bey.
His soldiers believe that water can't
drown him, fire can't burn him.
We hadn't had such an enemy
for a long time.
Beys!
Sharpen your swords.
Feel the vengeance.
If I can't tear him up and bait him
to the birds...
Do not call me Ertugrul Ghazi's son
Osman Bey.
Geyhatu sent this to hamper our
occupancy policy.
We're going to have a lot of troubles
now that Togay is here, my Bey.
There will be a meeting for Beys in Sogut.
Umur Bey said he'll accept my invitation.
All the Beys are coming to Sogut.
Except for Dodurga's Bey Ivaz.
We need to take precautions, brother.
- Don't worry, my Bey.
- Eyvallah, eyvallah (thank you).
Davut Bey, take Goktug out.
I need to talk to my brother.
Osman Bey.
As Osman Bey came this far and invited me
to the meeting...
he should be expecting a lot from me.
He probably will announce a conquest as
he invited all the Beys.
We'll see.
I wasn't sure whether you'd accept Osman
Bey's occupancy invitation....
after reading my letter.
There's no one to offer us something like
this.
Do you think Anatolian Beys will invite
Kızıl Bey to such an event?
Without permission, we can't even graze
our sheeps in Germiyanoglu, Konya.
Wherever we want to locate, there's always
an owner.
Isn't this land ours, father?
Are Ertugrul Ghazi and Osman Bey the
owner just because they defeated Byzantine?
Yes, of course daughter.
We must fight the infidels to gain land.
Look around.
Is there a stronger Bey than Osman?
No of course, but...
Osman Bey is surrounded with enemies and
betrayers. I am not sure Kayı's are safe.
Their safety is our safety.
It's all the same.
Whoever survives will carry
Turk's flag, daughter.
We were right about the treason issue
after Osman Bey survived an ambush.
Look at me. Treason doesn't come from
others.
It comes from the nearests.
Don't forget.
You were going to give me an evidence.
What was that?
I talked about an homicide in my latter.
I found this in the direction
of assassin.
Let's see whose finger fits.
That you killed Flatyos prevented me
from finding the betrayer, brother.
It was my right, Osman Bey.
That kill was my right.
Uncle Dündar thinks the same.
Did Uncle Dündar talk to you before
or after you killed Flatyos.
Does it matter, Osman Bey?
It does a lot, brother.
Just before I killed Flatyos.
If you are angry so much, let's use it
in a different way. Help me, brother.
Help me, brother, so that we can capture
the betrayer who caused Bayhoca's death.
I'd love to help you on that.
Good.
Now listen to me, brother.
Why didn't you attack Osman while getting
back from Umur Bey's?
Why did not you kill Osman?
The souls want brother blood, not
enemey blood.
What soul are you talking about,
Togay?
What is your aim if you're not intended
to kill Osman?
Killing someone with an arrow is
stupid.
An arrow of a master will set all the
tribes against each other.
Turks care a lot about their family.
This arrow will led to treason and
chaos.
Okay. Tell me.
I am listening to you.
If Osman dies, Gündüz takes over.
If Savcı dies, someone else will
take over.
Osman's death won't stop the dream
of his father Ertugrul.
What I want is not Osman's blood.
What I want is brother blood.
Osman...
Erlik Khan will give a terrible...
nightmare to Osman.
We heard about a meeting Osman
arranged in Sogut.
Osman Bey is taking precautions.
The Beys Osman is gathering for occupancy
will participate.
Except for Dodurga's Bey Ivaz.
What are you going to do while there are
too many precautions taken in Sogut, Togay?
Ivaz Bey will give me brother blood.
When Togay's arrow hits, Osman's and his
father's dreams will collapse.
All the Beys will turn against Osman Bey.
Is your aim going to be Ivaz Bey?
I will aim Ivaz Bey but shoot Umur Bey.
- How are you going to get in the meeting?
- A snake can pop up from any hole.
Then I shall show you the way
you'll crawl in like a snake.
Since we arrived in Sogut, we dig
tunnels everywhere.
Now you are here, this way goes to Church,
this one goes to the caravanserai
This tunnel leads you to the kitchen of
caravanserai.
Without alarming anyone.
Only snake-minded people like you
would think of that.
I don't want any trouble in Sogut.
We won't allow for treason.
My Bala, I want you to come t omorrow.
You can look after Hatuns.
Don't worry, my Bey. No one can attack
while I'm there.
No doubt, my Bala. You accomplished
every duty I assigned you.
What about Umur Bey?
I invited Umur bey too.
He'll come.
So we are going to see Malhun Hatun again.
Umur Bey doesn't have a son,
so his daughter will come.
If he had a son, Malhun Hatun wouldn't
be in the forefront.
She is a daughter of Bey, but you are
the daughter of Sheik Edebalı.
When she understands that, she'll
stop dominating you.
- Singing a Lullaby -
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of Allah the compassionate the merciful)
Our prophet says we'll be summoned with
our names and our father's name...
so we must name our children beautifully.
You name shall be Ertuğrul.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of Allah the compassionate the merciful)
Allah-u Akbar x4
(Allah is Great!)
Ashhadu an la ilaha illa Allah. x2
(I bear witness that there is no god except the One Allah)
Ashadu anna Muhammadan Rasool Allah. x2
(I bear witness that Muhammad is the messenger of Allah)
Hayya 'ala-s-Salah x2
(Hurry to the prayer)
Hayya 'ala-l-Falah. x2
(Hurry to salvation.)
Allah-u Akbar x2
(Allah is Great!)
La ilaha illa Allah.
(There's no god except for Allah)
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of Allah the compassionate the merciful)
Allah-u Akbar x4
(Allah is Great!)
Ashhadu an la ilaha illa Allah. x2
(I bear witness that there is no god except the One Allah)
Ashadu anna Muhammadan Rasool Allah. x2
(I bear witness that Muhammad is the messenger of Allah)
Hayya 'ala-s-Salah x2
(Hurry to the prayer)
Hayya 'ala-l-Falah. x2
(Hurry to salvation.)
As-salatu Khayrun Minan-nawm. x2
(Prayer is better than sleep.)
Allah-u Akbar x2
(Allah is Great!)
La ilaha illa Allah.
(There's no god except for Allah)
Your name is Ertugrul.
Savcı, if you allow, I want to visit
Sheik Edebalı soon.
Why, Hatun?
I heard Sheik in the funeral of Bayhoca.
In Quran, it says "Do not say of those who are
killed in the Way of Allah: They are dead!
Nay, they are alive, but you do not
perceive (their existence). [2/Al-Baqarah-154]
Our Lord said this in his book.
I want to know these,
I want to be a Muslim.
- No one will enter with their swords.
- Are Beys included, my Bey?
- Beys are included.
- As you command, my Bey.
Here is Osman's gift.
Gonca Hatun, what are you doing here?
We are here with Bala Hatun.
We are helping out.
Where is that smile coming from,
Boran Alp?
I started the wedding preparations
on the other hand.
Good, I did too.
As Osman Bey said, we are going to go to
both battle and wedding.
We'll kill the enemy, we'll give birth to
our children, we'll go on surviving Gonca.
Umur Bey, excuse me but I need to
take your swords.
Why is that?
Osman Bey commanded for the sake of
security.
Take it then.
This way.
He is coming!
You brought us peace.
Welcome.
Here.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of Allah, the merciful the compassionate.)
With the name of Allah's ninety nine name,
who is able to...
create, who fulfills our hearts
with faith.
How are you going to shoot it?
Just like that.
This arrow...
will erase Osman's dignity.
My Oghuz Father's heritage,
my valiant brothers.
You all accepted our invitation.
- Thank you.
- Eyvallah, (Thank you) Osman Bey.
Now you must be wondering the reason...
why I invted you to this meeting, and
the good news I'll deliver.
Here is the Inegol castle, where we are
going to weaken through...
our mind, destroy with our strenght.
Do not relieve with the strenght
of the crowd. My father is inside...
without his sword.
Keep your eyes wide open.
Yes, my Hanım.
Do you want anything, inshallah?
No, except for our swords.
Bala, this Hatun must know her limits.
She is guest, Gonca.
Let's mind our own business.
This is Sogut. We have Bozoyuk, Inegol,
and here Eskisehir in our south.
In the north, Bilecik and Yarhisar.
In the west, we have Bursa.
And there is Inegol between
us and Bursa.
The most savage infidel is
Inegol's Lord.
He is not only trying to break us through
great bazaars and trade routes...
He also tries to kill Muslim in
every chance he gets.
This castle has an important role.
After conquering it, we will be able
to move freely.
Alps.
See it yourself.
Who are you?
Inegol Lord is in Constantinie.
If we don't move, he'll come back to banish
all the Turkmen Beys from this land.
What do you mean by "move", Osman Bey?
What I am saying is that we should
gather our Alps.
We should come together,
and go to Inegol.
Break all the links between Inegol Castle
and Bilecik and Keles.
And we shall conquer Inegol Castle
while shouting "Allah Allah".
Osman Bey, Inegol Castle
is difficult to conquer.
However, a lion who conquered Kulucahisar
Castle...
can conquer Inegol castle, too.
I trust you with all my heart.
Your father Ertugrul Ghazi gifted Turks
Osman Bey, other than Kayı Tribe...
May Allah bless him.
Eyvallah, eyvallah (thank you)
Umur Bey.
Conquer is ours, victory is Allah's.
Inshallah.
(If Allah permits)
Inshallah, we will honour Inegol with
Islam and Turkishness.
Inshallah.
(If Allah permits)
And Inegol Castle will be the greates
castle we have ever conquered.
Inshallah, my Bey.
(If Allah permits)
Inshallah.
My Beys, we shall try,
Allah will decide.
Amin.
Alps!
It came from the kitchen!
Hurry!
Watch out Beys!
Soldier!
Take Beys out!
- Take Beys out!
- Father!
Hurry!
Father! Father!
Father, are you okay?
Hurry! Hurry!
Close the enterance and exit!
Hurry Alps!
Blow out the fire!
Cerkutay!
- Alps!
- Father, are you okay?
Father who did this to you?
Alps!
They came through the tunnel.
We'll find them, brother.
Hurry brother, hurry.
Where is the doctor?
Call the doctor!
Doctor!
Where is the doctor?
This way.
Umur Bey.
Daughter, the tribe is entrusted to you.
No, father no!
Hold on!
Where is the doctor?
Who are they?
Father, open your eyes!
Father!
You couldn't secure the meeting
Osman Bey!
Whose arrow is this?
Which infidel's is this arrow?
Hold on father!
Father, open your eyes!
Father, hold on, father!
Father open your eyes!
Hold on, father!
How can this happen despite all the
precautions?
How can this happen?
Tell me!
In my meeting, in my presence,
how can Beys be hurt?
How can be?
Answer me!
Bamsı Bey.
Brother.
Come here.
This is a Dodurga arrow.
Yıvaz Bey...
This is impossible, Osman Bey.
Even though he didn't join us, I don't
think Yıvaz Bey would do such a thing.
This is devil's job.
How can we be sure, my Bey?
Alps!
Get ready.
Unfortunately, he isn't doing great because
of the poison in the arrow. We'll wait.
- May Allah heal him.
- Are we going to wait? How, huh?
Do something.
Cure him!
I can't wait my father to die.
I'll prepare a remedy.
We'll find and punish whoever
did this to my father, Bahadır Bey.
Gather Alps at once.
Let's see what the issue is.
As you command, Malhun Hatun.
If something happens to you,
I'll set everywhere on fire.
We trusted Osman Bey's words and security.
We almost died.
So we shouldn't have trusted him. Most of
the Beys are returning.
We made a mistake.
A huge mistake.
We should have taken lessons from
the previous incident in which Beys died.
Now, this is not the right time to
talk about this.
Savcı Bey! Osman Bey is talking about
conquering Inegol Castle...
while he cannot even secure his
own meeting.
What are we going to talk about?
About that?
He is right. He is talking about
conquering Inegol Castle.
And he will. We want from you to
benefit the conquer.
This is good deeds, but he needs to
spot the enemy first.
Otherwise, we will end up like
Durhan and Ali Bey.
Osman Bey took revenge of martyred
Beys.
Why aren't you talking about that?
We need to think of something before
we die, Dündar Bey.
When Osman Bey comes back from Dodurga,
we'll tell him about our feelings as well.
Osman Bey!
Where are you going, Osman Bey?
You invited us, we came.
We trusted your securty, your words.
Is this how you secure people?
Malhun Hatun, do not talk while
you are angry.
My anger doesn't make me blind, Osman Bey.
My trust for you made me blind.
Otherwise, this would not have happened.
Malhun Hatun, get away.
Get away so that I find the betrayer.
Is there something you know?
Tell me.
I cannot accuse anyone without
knowing it for sure.
So you don't have an evidence, huh?
You only suspect.
I want evidence, Osman Bey.
I want blood.
Go now, Osman Bey.
Alps!
You spoiled our trust.
Go!
How can this happen, Bala? Who are we going
to trust if even Dodurga's Bey does this?
It's not clear yet, Gonca.
Osman Bey will figure it out.
Osman Bey.
He lost his dignity while...
he was trying to conquer
Inegol Castle.
Spread fear not only in Beys,
but also in Kayıs.
The Beys Osman invited to the meeting
will accuse him.
Osman is wise.
Sooner or later he will erase the fear...
we spread in his people.
Osman spoiled everyone's trust.
We will continue night and day.
We had a good partnership
with you Togay.
Not a partnership you can make with Togay,
only a good leather boots you make to me.
You know where to find me.
Provoke not only Beys, but also
the merchants.
The distrust against Osman...
will get in everybody's mind...
like a dark cloud...
all around.
Then the tribes will fall into each other.
Malhun Hatun is suspicious.
Malhun Hatun will attack Ivaz Bey...
with her alps because of my arrow.
Then Turks will drink each other's
blood.
What about you?
What are you going to do?
I'll meet Erlik Khan's dark souls.
Dark Souls are going to able me to
talk to my father.
My father will tell me how to kill Osman,
who is his biggest enemy Ertugrul's son.
Togay is Noyan's son, huh?
Not only his son.
He is also carries Noyan's soul...
in his ominous body.
Wake up Umur Bey, wake up.
If you don't, no one can sleep well.
I'll make them beg for their death,
to the ones who did this to you.
Can I come in?
Come.
- How are the Alps doing?
- Bahadır Bey gathered them all.
They are waiting for your command.
What is wrong with you?
Tell me.
They say Dodurga's Bey did this betrayal
to our Bey.
- Who said this?
- I heard Bala Hatun and Gonca Hatun.
Dodurga's Bey, huh?
Ivaz Bey.
That's why he didn't come.
I'll kill that betrayer, father.
Vengeance is my right.
We run away from Mongols and came
here for security.
But as we can see, the fire of treason
is burning this land.
Now it's time to put out the fire of
treason!
It's time to take revenge of our Bey!
Let's see how Umur Bey is doing.
Where are you going, Malhun Hatun.
Get away from my way.
I asked where you are going.
I'm going to take revenge of my father.
Get away from my way!
Hatun! Osman Bey will punish the
assassination on his own!
You exceeded your limits, Hatun!
Do whatever you need to do then!
Do not step in!
Stop, Gonca.
Malhun Hatun.
Bala Hatun.
You!
Malhun Hatun, Ivaz Bey is sinless.
Apparently, there's something wrong
about this.
They want us to suspect him.
I want vengeance Osman Bey. The game will
reveal itself when the revenge is taken.
Alps!
Stop.
Malhun Hatun, you can ask Umur Bey.
We are not so vile to shoot
a Turkmen Bey.
Ivaz Bey is right.
My suspect is apparent unless
you bring me the guilty.
Don't you trust me, Malhun Hatun?
My father trusted you and he is
at the death's door right now.
I understand your anger.
But our enemy is common. They're trying
to set us against each other.
The meeting is mine.
I am responsible for this.
First, we'll find out what's going on,
then we kill the guilty ones!
We shall trust you this time,
see what happens.
Everybody get back on their duty!
My Bala, calm down.
You wanted to talk to me.
I am listening.
Osman Bey, we trusted your word,
came here.
We gathered in a room, trusting
your security.
Umur Bey was shot with a poisonous arrow.
We almost died.
You think you made a mistake by
trusting me.
And the incidents we experienced today
proves you are right.
Then there is nothing to talk about.
Our visit shall ends here.
We want to go back to our tents.
If you leave now, what enemy wants
will happen then.
We don't even know our enemy, how
can you be sure about what they want?
We'll depart with the sunrise tomorrow.
We'll talk this through in our tent,
then decide.
But your dream, conquering Inegol,
is not likely to happen.
So...
you are telling me that I should
give up on my dream?
So, I should give up on my dream.
I am not telling you to give up on your
lives, I am not telling you that...
this unity is more important
than your lives....
I am not telling you that your lives are
worthless without this unity.
I am telling you to face your fears.
You are in fear because you can't unite.
You are nomad. You have no castle to
take cover when enemy attacks you.
You are open to any attack.
Infidels will come crowded.
They will tear your tents up!
Tell me...
From whom you are going to seek help,
if you don't unite?
United we stand, divided we fall.
If we unite, we become a state.
And infidels should know they are
attacking a state, not only a tent.
They'll know that we'll take
revenge.
And they won't dare to do it.
Don't you want that?
Of course we do, Osman Bey.
But...
But the enemy doesn't want this.
Right?
Of course they don't.
But we will push them!
We will insist!
We will push!
Beys! Brothers!
This is not only a dream.
But if you leave now...
this is going to remain as a dream
for our children.
I won't allow it.
Turks need a state.
Whoever turns his back on us,
Turks, who try to...
establish a state, is not going to
see good the days.
I won't give up.
No matter you join me or not.
Now tell me. Are you leaving
our unity?
Malhun Hatun, you got tired.
Eat and go to sleep.
I'll care.
I won't shut my eyes before my
father opens his eyes, Bahadır Bey.
- Daughter.
- Father.
My father, thanks to our Lord.
Who did this to me?
I suspected Dodurga's Bey.
What are you talking about, daughter?
We have been friends with Ivaz
since forever.
There's something wrong with this.
Osman Bey says it's not Ivaz.
He is right, daughter.
This is a planned assassination.
This is all because of Osman Bey's
recklessness, father.
Don't think about it now.
Just heal up.
My Bey, it's important.
- Tell me.
- We made an investigation.
We found some remnats of
the barrel with that arrow.
.
My Bey, this is Mongol's job.
This is Noyan's son's job.
Togay.
Cerkutay, you did a good job with Aygül.
Now I know who to kill.
Osman Bey keeps silent.
He had better be quick, father.
If he gets late, I'll take over.
I'll find that betrayer, punish him
myself.
Osman Bey has many enemies inside
and outside.
Now, we are getting hurt because
of that.
But, we did a great mistake by
trusting him.
- Can I come in?
- Come.
Excuse me, father.
Osman's Alp found a sign.
This is Togay's job.
Togay.
Get the Alps ready.
We'll set off with the sunrise tomorrow.
- We'll follow Togay.
- As you command, Malhun Hatun.
Togay.
We shed too much blood to get rid
of Noyan.
Now his son Togay shows up.
Bamsı Bey, Togay would shoot me
if he wanted to.
But he chose Umur bey.
- Do you think he wants Umur Bey?
- No, he wants me.
He doesn't want my life.
He wants Kayı Beys to lose dignity.
Yes, he wants the next Kayı Bey after
you to be undignified.
And so that your father's bequest
won't happen.
He wants Kayı Beys to be undignified
so we can't gather up.
They want to keep Muslim Turks
under their control.
Osman Bey, no one
can dare to do this, for sure.
But, they seem to succeed
at the moment.
My daughter, Allah is one
according to Islam.
He didn't give birth, he did not
born.
He is unique.
He is in need of nothing.
Contrarily, everything is in need of him.
Allah has no time, no place.
He is always with us.
He knows, he sees.
He is powerful enough to do
anything.
He is the one who gives everybody
their lives, who arranges everything.
My sweet daughter, Islam is accepting
the oneness of Allah, and giving in.
All the prophets ever since Hz. Adam
are honoured with...
Islam, the monotheism.
Each prophet invited people to the belief
of the oneness of Allah and...
notified people the commands and bans
they recieved from Allah.
Allah sent Hz Muhammed (s.a.v)...
as the last prophet...
to complete the prophet circle.
We Muslims accept all the prophets.
The last prophet
is Hz. Muhammad Mustafa (s.a.v)
Quran is the latest holy book that given
to our prophet by Allah.
We believe in everything in it without
hesitation.
We confirm angels, fate...
resurrection, which is doomsday.
Entering Islam is done by believing...
in Allah, Hz Muhammed Mustafa (s.a.v) is
his prophet...
and everything he brought us.
We utter this belief with shahada.
Now, my sweet daughter.
We will witness your shahada and
being Muslim.
In Allah's presence and in front of
the witness'...
you shall confirm you chose
the right religion...
under no influence and pressure.
I chose Islam...
under no pressure.
- Do you witness, Bala?
- Yes I do.
We witness.
Now, we will see you becoming a Muslim...
and saying shahada.
Ashhadu an la ilaha illa Allah
(I bear witness that there is no god except the One Allah)
Ashadu anna Muhammadan Rasool Allah.
(I bear witness that Muhammad is the messenger of Allah)
It shall be blessed.
Our holy book Quran says that when we
become Muslim...
we get rid of all of our sins.
and our prophet (s.a.v)
confirms this.
Brother, here, tell me.
I completed my duty, my Bey. Uncle Dündar is
seeing Merchant Suleiman and Melik constantly.
He went to them today as well.
My uncle is dealing with our
trading issues.
He may see merchants, there's nothing
wrong with that.
Yes, but he goes to them like they
are the only merchants in the world.
We know we don't trust them, Osman Bey.
Whenever we see their face, a trouble
finds us afterward.
They raided our caravan, my Bey.
They stole our fund.
They tortured us, my Bey.
You can't have justice with guilt.
You can't kill someone just
because of your suspicions.
Togay...
raided the tent.
Thanks to Cerkutay, we know that.
A traitor from this tent let
Togay know, then.
Obviously, Togay and Nikola work together.
Brother.
Do you remember that...
we threw apples into the water before
eating them when we were young.
So that we can get rid of the worms.
If we don't get rid of the worms about
my uncle inside us...
that worm will eat us out.
Then...
we'll throw the apples into the water.
If the traitor is my uncle...
if the killer of my son is my uncle...
it's my right to cut his head off, my Bey.
We'll learn it, brother.
We will.
We'll play such a trick that...
we'll understand if my
uncle is a traitor and...
we'll have Geyhatu's dog Togay...
and kill him!
But how, my Bey?
I will tell you, brother.
Tell my uncle and Gündüz brother...
they should come here.
- Do not let the black
mountains be destroyed...-
- Do not cut down the
big tree with shade.-
A bird comes, another bird flies.
- Do not let the black
mountains be destroyed...-
Togay...
raided the tent and feast.
Are you sure?
Yes, uncle.
How could Geyhatu's dogs...
know about our...
feast?
We will learn it, uncle.
We will learn it.
He was close to us.
Why did he just leave without killing?
Their intention is obvious. They want
Beys to not trust us.
Unbelievers say...
"Osman Bey can't protect you.
Leave these lands."
They say that the
tents who accepted our invite...
won't come here.
Now...
Tell the Beys in Söğüt.
Gündüz brother, tell Alps.
We will protect the Beys on the road.
We will accompany them to their tents.
Your command, my Bey.
When the dawn breaks, we
will pass Karacabel.
Then we will stop a while and rest.
We will leave Demir Bey in his tent and
we will come back, Inshallah.
Inshallah.
Uncle.
Take care of the tent while we are away.
Don't worry, nephew.
You should bring the Beys to
their tents safe and sound.
Don't worry, uncle.
I don't worry about it.
However, we should be...
careful this time.
Yes.
That's all I want to say.
If you excuse us, Osman Bey.
You can go.
Osman Bey.
My Bey.
They say the things are crazy in Söğüt.
Osman will never gain back...
the reliance of Beys that he invited.
You can't gain back the trust
when you break it once.
You know.
We know the intention.
The last time Osman invited the Beys...
all of them were killed.
Now, Umur Bey got what he was
supposed to get.
Osman showed his dignity but...
then lost it.
What does he want from you?
He wants to take Beys to their tent
safe and sound...
just to gain his reputation back.
He will look after Beys.
He told me to take care of the tent.
Mashallah.
He trusts you.
Osman isn't a fool, Hatun.
Neither I am.
What do you mean, Dündar Bey?
I have to send news to Süleyman.
You have lots of burdens, Osman Bey.
I'm sorry that I can't do anything.
The enemy will play a trick...
and we will ruin it.
They will do it again and...
we will ruin it again.
That's what will happen all the time.
You convinced Beys to stay in Söğüt.
Now you seem as
if you have found the traitor.
We know who shot Umur Bey.
Tomorrow, we will find who the
traitor is, Inshallah.
Who do you suspect?
I can't tell what I think of.
If...
If I'm right about my suspicions...
I worry what will happen then.
I'm afraid...
of my anger.
Is he someone close to us?
The person you suspect?
Yes, Bala.
Close?
He is someone close to us.
Alps are ready, Malhun Hatun.
We will follow the evil Togay.
We will kill him before
my father gets better.
You won't come with me.
Did I do something wrong?
No. You'll stay here with Bahadır Bey
because I fully trust you.
Take care of my father.
Malhun Hatun, I've never
left you alone before.
Togay is violent.
Don't.
Do what I say.
How will you find them?
I will look everywhere!
Everything is ready.
We are safe.
Let's go if you are ready.
- We're ready, Osman Bey.
- Thank you.
Did you find...
the traitor, Osman Bey?
I will, Malhun Hatun.
Don't worry.
However, I want something.
Don't leave your father alone.
Sure, Osman Bey but you can't
lose someone's trust twice.
Malhun Hatun.
Where are we going?
I said we're going to find
my father's killer. Didn't you hear?
Forgive me. I sacrifice
myself for you and our Bey.
However, we don't
know the way.
We don't even know whom we are following.
You're right.
However, the enemies know us well.
My father's killers want to destroy the
dignity of Osman Bey and...
they want to harm our union.
They know that I follow my father's way.
They know that we will build
a tent with Osman Bey.
They want me now.
They will follow me.
You sacrifice yourself for your father.
Not just for my father, also for our tent.
Get ready now.
It's time for revenge.
She is coming.
The forest road is bleeding.
Alps are on their way.
Two hunters are following them.
Dündar.
He is the cruelest traitor I know.
I love traitors who serve me.
Let's go.
Come on!
Kayı forests will be full of blood.
Stop.
Alps!
We will wait here.
- Boran.
- Yes, my Bey.
Protect the Beys.
- They won't get any harm.
- Your command, my Bey.
If the traitor...
is my uncle...
Togay will know that we
will locate here with the Beys.
He may attack at any time.
A Bey of Kayı...
the son of Suleyman Shah...
our uncle...
how could he do it?
Does it make sense?
If he isn't the traitor...
neither it is me nor you...
now my brother...
and Bamsı Bey.
If my uncle is the traitor, it means
he is the killer of my son Bayhoca.
We should punish him.
What his punishment is clear.
It is.
When you tried to kill him...
I was mad at you.
I thought you were going too far
as you had no evidence.
However...
if the traitor is my
uncle, I will kill him.
We don't know yet, brother.
We don't.
When the enemy comes, we'll know.
I think they will come.
I will kill them first...
then my uncle.
We will get it.
We will.
Trap!
Protect Malhun Hatun!
Where is Togay?
He is close as death.
Stop.
Evil!
Revenge is blinding.
It blinds beautiful eyes.
I knew you'd follow me.
Why doesn't Osman want...
me to follow him, Petrus?
Dündar Bey.
Osman knows that after
he falls from grace...
you will want to kill him, Togay.
Dündar thinks that Osman
fools him to catch you.
Osman will entrap me.
He will fool Dündar and he will expose me.
Wow.
His uncle is as shrewd as Osman.
We need Dündar.
We shouldn't expose him.
I destroyed the relationship between
Osman and Umur Bey.
Now it's time for her daughter.
Malhun Hatun.
Göktuğ saw me.
Cerkutay will understand that I did
the assassination.
Malhun will be angry at me.
She will
follow me to take revenge.
- Without knowing your place?
- She will know.
While Osman is waiting in the place
that he will entrap me at...
I will fight Malhun Hatun.
First, her father and then his daughter.
Kızılbeyoğulları and Kayıs...
will never be together.
I smell blood to my lungs.
I'll cut your lungs off and
make you eat them, Togay!
A filly should have a saddle.
I'll let you live, woman.
Tell Osman that...
Geyhatu knows what he is doing.
I will kill all of the people
in the tents...
who come for Osman's invite.
Kill me, Togay.
I will kill you if you don't kill me.
Let's go.
They may attack at any time.
We're here for their dead bodies...
but the soil we're on has got wormy.
What does that mean, Cerkutay?
You become angry quickly.
We aren't facing off against
Byzantine's fancy dogs.
We are facing off against Togay.
Don't you think Togay took the bait?
Cerkutay doesn't know.
Togay's voice stops the wind.
Togay's breath burns the forests.
Osman Bey knows what he is doing.
Black Shaman Togay.
He does his job with black spirits.
I think my uncle hasn't sent news.
I wonder if...
our suspicions are in vain.
Looks like they are, Osman Bey.
I have to send news to Süleyman.
You can't leave the tent as
you may attract attention.
You will send the news, not me.
I don't feel sorry as
we're here for no reason.
I feel happy
because our uncle isn't a traitor.
- My Alps will accompany you to your tents.
- Thank you, Osman Bey
Thank you.
Alps!
We're going back.
Come on.
Stop!
Malhun Hatun!
Malhun Hatun! Malhun Hatun!
Lie down.
Are you fine?
Malhun Hatun! Malhun Hatun!
She is alive.
Get ready Alps!
- Malhun Hatun.
- What happened? Tell me.
Who did this?
Togay killed my Alps.
All of them.
Togay?
My uncle isn't a traitor, Osman Bey.
My uncle isn't a traitor.
Togay followed Malhun Hatun.
- Saltuk.
- My Bey.
Tell Cerkutay.
- He should find the trace of Togay.
- Your command, my Bey.
Hold on.
Malhun Hatun.
You will live.
Bala! Help her. She
lost lots of blood.
Come on, Bala!
Help her.
Malhun Hatun.
Come on, my Bala.
Open your eyes.
- Osman Bey.
- Yes. Tell me.
Why didn't Togay kill you?
Togay...
wanted me to tell you...
What will you say?
Geyhatu...
knows what you're doing.
He said...
He will kill all of the people
in the tents...
who came for Osman's invite.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com